That was the first time...
What?
I've never told anyone how I felt.
You were the first person I've ever been completely honest with.
Yusuke...
Thank you for that, Haruyo.
It's beautiful.
This novel they play with are you still...
I can't become a shadow.
I hang the same time.
I've triggered my Sorry.
Your意思 is a Zuk.
In the dark place.
Never knew how to take a home.
I'm not turning right away anymore.
Oh
oh
Roo, dear, that's sweet of you,
but you're going to be late for school.
Huh? What time is it?
You get going. I'll take care of the rest.
Thanks!
Oh, good morning, Roo.
Hey, Tama. School time.
Can't I sleep just another five minutes?
I guess, but you're coming with either way.
Um, Yuzuki, I'm sorry.
I'm taking off.
All alone today, huh?
Where's your sister? Shouldn't you two be together?
Huh? The heck's that supposed to mean?
Ah, kids.
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Akira's still missing?
Wow.
Yeah, they interviewed a girl from her school in that article.
It's like she just disappeared.
Nobody's seen her for almost a week.
You're going to miss the train. Roo!
Now departing.
Yuzuki.
We were getting along so well, but now...
God, I hate this. We can't be friends anymore.
No, we can't.
She's right, because...
I refuse to have any more battles.
But Yuzuki won't stop battling until her wish comes true.
No matter how many people she hurts in the process.
But I... I can't live like that.
You serious?
Pretty freaky, huh?
The twins?
Yeah, can you believe they're a couple?
Like, incest for real?
No way.
Wow, so the rumors are true?
Whoa, you think they've already done it?
Duh, what do you think?
Oh, barf.
Don't blame yourself, Honoka.
There's no way you could have known he was like that.
And I used to think he was cool.
He's just gross.
I assume you're the one responsible for all this?
It's not her fault, jackass.
Yeah, people wouldn't talk if you and your sister acted normal.
No, jerk. I didn't do a thing.
I just told a few friends what you said to me.
You know, how upset you got when you heard the rumor.
Honoka was worried about you, you jerk.
I really wasn't trying to start anything.
Although your sister does act kind of weird sometimes.
You know, forget you. I'm done.
Nobody talks bad about my sister.
Don't act like I'm some kind of villain.
So rude.
Jeez, you're horrible.
No wonder people are saying he and his sister are an item.
Apologize to her.
What a weirdo.
You made my skin crawl.
Yeah, with her brother.
Aw, nasty.
Too bad. I thought she was hot.
There you are.
Yusuke.
So I heard you've been telling people not to talk about me. Is that for real?
Yeah.
That's sweet of you, but it's not really necessary.
It's not gossip if it's true.
Wait a minute. What do you mean by that?
I mean, I'm in love with you.
What?
I've been in love with you ever since we were kids, but I never told you before.
I didn't want to scare you off, but I've felt this way my entire life. Always.
You've got a crush on that cute boy Goto, don't you?
Uh-huh.
And you, Yusuke?
While my friends were always chatting about what boy they had a crush on that week.
Come on, spill it.
Huh?
Everyone said who they liked. Now it's your turn.
Who's your secret crush?
Uh, sorry, but I don't have one. At least not right now.
Liar, liar. Pants on fire.
I'm just not really into any of the guys in my class.
You're so lying.
No, I'm not. Tell the truth.
I am, doofus.
I couldn't tell anyone how I really felt.
So, um, your brother, do you know if there's a girl he likes?
Um, well, to tell the truth, he's always talking about how girls are gross.
Even when he's watching TV, if, like, a kissing scene comes on, he always changes the channel.
I lied to all my friends, and...
I lied to you. The one I love.
Oh!
For the longest time, I thought maybe it was best to keep it like that.
Are you sure? Can you really live like this?
Yeah.
But no matter what, I will still live Kazuki forever.
And it doesn't matter if he finds a girlfriend, or gets married, or even if he has kids.
I'll just keep living this lie for the rest of my life, till I'm old and alone.
If this is the only way I can love him, so be it, I guess.
But then, one day...
A card game?
Yeah, it's pretty fun.
You must be my selector.
Huh?
My name's Hanio. Nice to meet you.
Whoa, that card just talked to me.
Wait, the card did what now?
It talked. You mean... you didn't hear? I'm not crazy.
He can't hear me. As a matter of fact, the only ones who can are selectors like you.
Okay, but what have I been selected for?
My wish can come true?
Mm-hmm. Whether you believe that or not, though, is entirely up to you.
You do have a wish, right?
I'm stuck inside a card. Your secret is safe with me.
I...
Love.
What?
Kazuki, I...
Love him.
Okay, so who...
Oh, wait, you mean your brother.
Yes, I love him.
I love Kazuki.
I love my brother, okay?
I know, I know it's not right, and I know it's not normal, but I still want to be with him. I want to spend the rest of my life with him. I want more than that. I want to be Kazuki's girlfriend.
I want to spend the rest of my life with him. I want to be...
so then your wish was for you once called my strategy straightforward that's how I
have to be in life too I have to be straightforward with you the same way I
was with Hanio that was the first time what I've never told anyone how I felt
you were the very first person I've ever been completely honest with
Yuzuki thank you for that Hanio I didn't care what it would take to
accomplish if there was any chance of being with you even if it meant me
getting hurt or dying I'd take it because I love you do you feel the same about me
Kazuki no he hasn't come back from lunch yet oh thanks OMG would you look who's here it's the
brother lover so Stevie a wish one that you want so badly that you're willing to
hurt yourself or someone else next time we meet I'll be a new me no more regrets I'll
finally be Kazuki's girlfriend for real I tried to stop her but I couldn't she didn't care what happened
I guess since I don't have a wish I can't understand but it is the nature of battle and our nature as well
both mine both mine and yours I'm not like her
you're feeling sad huh what you know cuz you and Yuzuki and Hitoi were all friends but now you're not
Tama will still be your friend though let's battle well even if we don't get to battle we're friends
forever Tama I'm sorry I like to battle so much but you did so I'll just stop
thank you Tama thank you Tama you rock yep excuse me
Hitoi what the why are you here wait a minute does this mean you're all better now and you remember me
look Hitoi has an L rig but how you you're a selector aren't you please let me challenge you to a battle
battle me please just say yes I can't no I won't
look I'm real sorry but I've decided not to battle people ever again oh yeah then why are you still
keeping Tama around Yuzuki guess I can't blame you you two are practically best friends
where are you speaking of friends can't you do a favor for two of your former ones just for old
time's sake come on where are you Yuzuki no hey hey long time no see no not really you're an L rig this can't be real it's nuts I mean
that can't be you it's me all right here let me prove it
that's crunchy it's yeah the one I bought with you two that day
guess the three of us can't stay apart huh Yuzuki what happened suppose I owe you an explanation and
I'll be happy to give you one if you agree to a battle with heat away and risk hurting her there's no
freaking way you'd be doing it to help her so her wish can be granted and so mine can too I need to
fight Ruko please if it's for my friends I
if it's for my friends I
fine I'll do it
fine thank you
open
damn it all I hate this
okay grow Tama
on it
all right Yuzuki now you tell me what happened
well for starters I won my final battle and then at long last my wish came true
since you've made your decision let us join together for one final attack
now the oath do you remember it yeah it's a I accept the laws of the selector
The Laws of the Selector.
I accept the Laws of the Selector.
And, um...
And upon this sacred oath, the new Eternal Girl shall be born!
Adamasere!
What?
Then does that mean you're not the only Yuzuki?
Not anymore.
So Hanayo?
Became you?
Obviously, that wasn't what I was expecting.
But after we finished the oath,
I found out what it really means to become an Eternal Girl.
My wish?
Now it gets granted to her.
I made this drawing in preschool.
The princess is supposed to be me.
And this black scribble.
You want to guess?
It's supposed to be of you as my prince.
This drawing is of us on our wedding day.
But the other kids told me it was dirty and wrong.
So I did this.
Scribbled over it.
Tried to cover it up.
Again and again.
But...
It was still there.
Yeah, I get it.
Try as I might.
These feelings won't go away either.
Yuzuki.
I love you.
And in the same way you love me.
I mean it.
I've felt this way a long time.
But because we're family,
I kept those feelings to myself just like you.
I did my best to block them out.
But to hell with that.
I can't do it anymore.
I love you.
Listen.
I don't care what people think.
Or what they say.
If it means I have to give up anything and everything to be with you,
so be it.
I love you, Yuzuki.
I love you.
I swear it.
I love you too, Yuzuki.
So very much.
I'm so happy.
The wish has finally come true.
So not just your life.
She took your wish all for herself?
And now you become an Elric.
Once the Selector is replaced,
they become another person's Elric.
Nice to meet you, Selector.
So whether we win or lose,
it's the Selectors who suffer,
and the Elrics who benefit.
Maybe they were fighting to become human again all along.
And yet she did grant my wish.
Holding up her end of this perverse contract, I suppose.
And I became an Eternal Girl
to repeat the cycle.
Get it now?
That's the ugly truth behind this game!
I don't know.
I'll see you next time.